[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "Is that correct, do we think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "I don't want to speculate and that is speculation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "From what you saw, do you fear that the death toll is going to rise?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "I do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "RB", "CC", "VBD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "When you got back to your hotel and began to realize the scale of the disaster that unfold, what was your reaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "Well, I guess I kind of mulled it over a little bit by then and wasn't -- I didn't know what was going on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 102, "question": "I've had a lot of contacts here, yes, since today's incident, you mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", ",", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "I want to bring in --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "John, would you like to talk to Bill and tell him what you saw?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "I just -- I feel bad for Bill that he couldn't enjoy his marathon finish.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "RP", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "CC", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "What are your feelings about the people or the persons that perpetrated this act?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "Yes, I thought about that myself, because it's just -- everybody else is out there having fun and you got one or two people that are trying to destroy the whole thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "Will you continue to run marathons after this, Bill?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "Oh, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "You think that should be the attitude of everyone in America, to what has happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "TO", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "Oh, well, I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "WDT", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 132, "question": "As you were taking it, what was going through your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 133, "answer": "Well, Piers, I'm on the finish line at that point and I'm just taking the late finishers of which there were another 9,000 people still yet to cross the finish line.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBP", "RB", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "Do we know any hard evidence yet that could lead us to a potential suspect?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "Well, there are clearly persons of interest.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 175, "question": "ORGAN: Paul Cruikshank, from all that you've seen and heard so far, where is it leading your head as to potentially what is behind this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "TO", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 176, "answer": "We just don't know who was responsible for this, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paul Cruikshank"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "JJ", "NNP", "VBD", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 185, "question": "Any significance to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 186, "answer": "Well, you know, Piers, here in New York, we had this disrupted subway plot which was, in fact, al Qaeda related and it involved backpack bombs.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "CD", ",", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 234, "question": "Can you tell me when you first heard what had happened today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 235, "answer": "I was standing about 20, 25 feet from the initial blast, so I knew immediately what was going on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["BOSTON"]}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "What was your reaction when you heard the first explosion go off?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "HERESA PAINTER, BOSTON MARATHON RUNNER: Well, I really wasn't paying attention and then when I heard the bomb and saw the reaction of the spectators, I was just alarmed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 249, "question": "Were you treating people there today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBG", "NNS", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 250, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJS", "CD", "TO", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 255, "question": "What was the type of injury, how many people did you see injured there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 256, "answer": "I saw at least six to seven people down next to me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "Have you ever seen injuries like this in your time working in Boston?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Boston"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "POS", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 269, "question": "What is the reaction, do you think, of the people of Boston to what's happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 270, "answer": "Well, I think including myself, I think everybody's really sad.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Boston"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "Was this akin to some of the things you've witnessed on battlefields?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "TO", "WP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 291, "question": "Was that going through your mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 292, "answer": "You know, after the initial explosion, for me, it was a little unclear as to what happened.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Boston"]}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "But what are you picking up from the White House about this, anything?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "Picking up from law enforcement authorities in the government that, across this country, a number of selected cities are actually beefing up their security presence in light of what has happened in Boston.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "How serious a blow is this to America's ongoing war on terror?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "TO", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "Oh, I think it's just too early to tell.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "Will they all have to now be submitted to much higher degrees of security?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "RB", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "Well, I think that we have to get used to the idea that when we fight terrorism, there's no 100 percent protection that we can provide the public.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CD", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "JJR", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "In terms of how they go forward, are those two areas going to be key?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "VBP", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "Those two, and I would add one more, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "RBR", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", ",", "DT", "RBR", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "RB", "RBR", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "Because could they have, from those devices, if they got there in time and could study them -- can that be a key lead, as Fran was suggesting, to getting to where this came from?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NN", "CC", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ":", "MD", "IN", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", ",", "TO", "VBG", "TO", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "The more devices there were, the more ambitious this attack would have been, maybe more people would have been involved but it's not impossible that a lone wolf could do this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ed Davis"]}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", ",", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "How significant could that be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "IN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "Well, Ed Davis, the police commissioner who I have worked with a lot of years I think debunked that, said that everyone in the hospital is being questioned.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["April 15th"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NNP", "CD", "VBZ", "NN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "Could it be somebody using that as some reason to make a point?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "Oh, Piers, it's also April 15th is tax day, where we pay our taxes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "Paul, although we don't know yet, very quickly, how soon would you expect us to have a much clearer idea?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "WRB", "RB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "Well, it's difficult to tell how the investigation is going to go.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Newtown"]}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "What do you feel about somebody that would target such an event, knowing that people like that are there and that so many of the runners from all over the world are raising huge amounts of money for charity?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "VBP", "RB", "CC", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "UGHES: It's the devastating part about it, especially for Newtown which is not too far from my hometown.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "What do we know about the likelihood of more fatalities and more importantly, hopefully, people who can be saved tonight from injuries that you know of?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJR", "NNS", "CC", "JJR", "RB", ",", "RB", ",", "NNS", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "Well, if there was any good news in all this, it's that there was a lot of medical triage sort of at the site, as you have been talking about as well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Boston", "Massachusetts"]}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "What is your reaction to what's happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "It is a terrible day for the city of Boston, for the Commonwealth of Massachusetts, for our country and for the sport of running globally.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "What did you make of that, Fred?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "You know, I think he speaks a lot to the spirit of the marathon and the connection that so many people feel to this particular run and this particular distance.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Boston Marathon"]}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "CD", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "Finally, Fred, will there be a Boston Marathon next year?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "MD", "VB", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "The Boston Marathon has endured two world wars and many other things.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Fred"], "LOCATION": ["Boston"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "Fran Townsend, before we go to a quick break, a quick question for you, if it had been a foreign organization, terrorist group that had done this, would you expect them to claim responsibility by now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "VBN", "DT", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "Not clear, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Fran Townsend"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "Matt Frucci, obviously you're more -- can you hear me, matt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", ":", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "I can hear you, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Matt Frucci"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 550, "question": "What was it like for you to be caught up in such a horrific incident?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 551, "answer": "It was quite terrifying.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Patriots Day"], "LOCATION": ["Massachusetts"]}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "Matt, what do you think this will do to a great American sporting event like this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "You know, as a Massachusetts resident, Patriots Day is a huge thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "Is this going to dramatically change the way that events like the Boston Marathon will have to be handled in the future?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "Well, Piers, open course events like a marathon or non-stadium events certainly have these risks.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Boston Marathon"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130415pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "Would you be advising them to go ahead?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "I think it depends on the risk profile.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]